question_data = [
    {"category": "Entertainment: Video Games", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "hard",
     "question": "The retail disc of Tony Hawk&#039;s Pro Skater 5 only comes with the tutorial.",
     "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]},
    {"category": "Vehicles", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "hard",
     "question": "In 1993 Swedish car manufacturer Saab experimented with replacing the steering wheel with a joystick in a Saab 9000.",
     "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]},
    {"category": "Entertainment: Video Games", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "hard",
     "question": "In &quot;The Sims&quot; series, the most members in a household you can have is 8.",
     "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]},
    {"category": "History", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "hard",
     "question": "Japan was part of the Allied Powers during World War I.", "correct_answer": "True",
     "incorrect_answers": ["False"]},
    {"category": "General Knowledge", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "hard",
     "question": "This is the correct spelling of &quot;Supercalifragilisticexpialidocious&quot.",
     "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]},
    {"category": "History", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "hard",
     "question": "Joseph Stalin&#039;s real name was Ioseb Bessarionis dze Dzugashvili.", "correct_answer": "True",
     "incorrect_answers": ["False"]},
    {"category": "Entertainment: Comics", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "hard",
     "question": "In the comic book &quot;Archie&quot;, Betty is friends with Veronica because she is rich.",
     "correct_answer": "False", "incorrect_answers": ["True"]},
    {"category": "Entertainment: Video Games", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "hard",
     "question": "The first &quot;Metal Gear&quot; game was released for the PlayStation 1.", "correct_answer": "False",
     "incorrect_answers": ["True"]}, {"category": "Science: Mathematics", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "hard",
                                      "question": "The binary number &quot;101001101&quot; is equivalent to the Decimal number &quot;334&quot;",
                                      "correct_answer": "False", "incorrect_answers": ["True"]},
    {"category": "Science: Mathematics", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "hard",
     "question": "If you could fold a piece of paper in half 50 times, its&#039; thickness will be 3\/4th the distance from the Earth to the Sun.",
     "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]},
    {"category": "History", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "hard",
     "question": "The fourth funnel of the RMS Titanic was fake designed to make the ship look more powerful and symmetrical.",
     "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]},
    {"category": "Entertainment: Video Games", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "hard",
     "question": "In Undertale, having a &quot;Fun Value&quot; set to 56-57 will play the &quot;Wrong Number Song Call&quot;.",
     "correct_answer": "False", "incorrect_answers": ["True"]},
    {"category": "Entertainment: Video Games", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "hard",
     "question": "TF2: Sentry rocket damage falloff is calculated based on the distance between the sentry and the enemy, not the engineer and the enemy",
     "correct_answer": "False", "incorrect_answers": ["True"]},
    {"category": "Mythology", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "hard",
     "question": "Rannamaari was a sea demon that haunted the people of the Maldives and had to be appeased monthly with the sacrifice of a virgin girl.",
     "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]},
    {"category": "Entertainment: Video Games", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "hard",
     "question": "Danganronpa 2: Goodbye Despair featured all of the surviving students from the first game.",
     "correct_answer": "False", "incorrect_answers": ["True"]},
    {"category": "Entertainment: Japanese Anime & Manga", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "hard",
     "question": "Throughout the entirety of &quot;Dragon Ball Z&quot;, Goku only kills two characters: a miniboss named Yakon and Kid Buu.",
     "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]},
    {"category": "Entertainment: Music", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "hard",
     "question": "The song &quot;Mystery Train&quot; was released by artist &quot;Little Junior&#039;s Blue Flames&quot; in 1953.",
     "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]},
    {"category": "Entertainment: Film", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "hard",
     "question": "&quot;Cube&quot;, &quot;Cube 2: Hypercube&quot; and &quot;Cube Zero&quot; were directed by the same person.",
     "correct_answer": "False", "incorrect_answers": ["True"]},
    {"category": "Science: Computers", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "hard",
     "question": "The IBM PC used an Intel 8008 microprocessor clocked at 4.77 MHz and 8 kilobytes of memory.",
     "correct_answer": "False", "incorrect_answers": ["True"]},
    {"category": "General Knowledge", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "hard",
     "question": "In Scandinavian languages, the letter &Aring; means river.", "correct_answer": "True",
     "incorrect_answers": ["False"]}, {"category": "History", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "hard",
                                       "question": "The Battle of Trafalgar took place on October 23rd, 1805",
                                       "correct_answer": "False", "incorrect_answers": ["True"]},
    {"category": "Entertainment: Video Games", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "hard",
     "question": "The names of Roxas&#039;s Keyblades in Kingdom Hearts are &quot;Oathkeeper&quot; and &quot;Oblivion&quot;.",
     "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]},
    {"category": "Politics", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "hard",
     "question": "Joko Widodo has appeared in the cover of a TIME magazine.", "correct_answer": "True",
     "incorrect_answers": ["False"]}, {"category": "Entertainment: Music", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "hard",
                                       "question": "The band STRFKR was also briefly known as Pyramiddd.",
                                       "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]},
    {"category": "Entertainment: Books", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "hard",
     "question": "Harry Potter was born on July 31st, 1980.", "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]},
    {"category": "Entertainment: Video Games", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "hard",
     "question": "All of these maps were in &quot;Tom Clancy&#039;s Rainbow Six Siege&quot; on its initial release: House, Clubhouse, Border, Consulate.",
     "correct_answer": "False", "incorrect_answers": ["True"]},
    {"category": "Entertainment: Japanese Anime & Manga", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "hard",
     "question": "Druid is a mage class in &quot;Log Horizon&quot;.", "correct_answer": "False",
     "incorrect_answers": ["True"]}, {"category": "Entertainment: Television", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "hard",
                                      "question": "The Klingon home planet is Qo&#039;noS.", "correct_answer": "True",
                                      "incorrect_answers": ["False"]},
    {"category": "Entertainment: Board Games", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "hard",
     "question": "The board game Go has more possible legal positions than the number of atoms in the visible universe.",
     "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]},
    {"category": "Celebrities", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "hard",
     "question": "Lady Gaga&#039;s real name is Stefani Joanne Angelina Germanotta.", "correct_answer": "True",
     "incorrect_answers": ["False"]}, {"category": "Science: Mathematics", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "hard",
                                       "question": "In Topology, the complement of an open set is a closed set.",
                                       "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]},
    {"category": "General Knowledge", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "hard",
     "question": "Stagecoach owned &quot;South West Trains&quot; before losing the rights to FirstGroup and MTR in March of 2017.",
     "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]},
    {"category": "Science: Mathematics", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "hard",
     "question": "L&#039;H&ocirc;pital was the mathematician who created the homonymous rule that uses derivatives to evaluate limits with indeterminations.",
     "correct_answer": "False", "incorrect_answers": ["True"]},
    {"category": "Politics", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "hard",
     "question": "George Clinton, Vice President of the United States (1805-1812), is an ancestor of President Bill Clinton.",
     "correct_answer": "False", "incorrect_answers": ["True"]},
    {"category": "Entertainment: Music", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "hard",
     "question": "Pete Townshend&#039;s solo album, &quot;White City: A Novel&quot;, is set in the metropolitan area of Chicago.",
     "correct_answer": "False", "incorrect_answers": ["True"]},
    {"category": "Entertainment: Japanese Anime & Manga", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "hard",
     "question": "In the &quot;To Love-Ru&quot; series, Peke is considered a female robot.", "correct_answer": "True",
     "incorrect_answers": ["False"]}, {"category": "General Knowledge", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "hard",
                                       "question": "Spoon theory is a theory, utilizing &quot;Spoons&quot; as a metaphor for energy they can use in a day.",
                                       "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]},
    {"category": "Geography", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "hard",
     "question": "The two largest ethnic groups of Belgium are Flemish and Walloon. ", "correct_answer": "True",
     "incorrect_answers": ["False"]}, {"category": "Mythology", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "hard",
                                       "question": "Janus was the Roman god of doorways and passageways.",
                                       "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]},
    {"category": "Entertainment: Music", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "hard",
     "question": "The singer Billie Holiday was also known as &quot;Lady Day&quot;.", "correct_answer": "True",
     "incorrect_answers": ["False"]},
    {"category": "Entertainment: Japanese Anime & Manga", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "hard",
     "question": "The character Plum from &quot;No Game No Life&quot; is a girl.", "correct_answer": "False",
     "incorrect_answers": ["True"]}, {"category": "Vehicles", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "hard",
                                      "question": "The term &quot;GTO&quot; was originated by Ferrari?",
                                      "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]},
    {"category": "Art", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "hard",
     "question": "The Statue of Liberty&#039;s official name is &ldquo;Liberty Enlightening the World&rdquo;.",
     "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]},
    {"category": "History", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "hard",
     "question": "The man that shot Alexander Hamilton was named Aaron Burr.", "correct_answer": "True",
     "incorrect_answers": ["False"]}, {"category": "Geography", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "hard",
                                       "question": "Only one country in the world starts with the letter Q.",
                                       "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]},
    {"category": "Entertainment: Film", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "hard",
     "question": "YouTube personality Jenna Marbles served as an executive producer of the film Maximum Ride (2016).",
     "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]},
    {"category": "Entertainment: Video Games", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "hard",
     "question": "The Paradox Interactive game &quot;Stellaris&quot; was released in 2016.", "correct_answer": "True",
     "incorrect_answers": ["False"]},
    {"category": "Entertainment: Japanese Anime & Manga", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "hard",
     "question": "The protagonist in &quot;Humanity Has Declined&quot; has no discernable name and is simply referred to as &#039;I&#039; for most of the series.",
     "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]},
    {"category": "Entertainment: Video Games", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "hard",
     "question": "In The Witcher 3, the Zoltan Chivay Gwent card can be found under the Hanged Man&#039;s Tree.",
     "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]},
    {"category": "General Knowledge", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "hard",
     "question": "NCIS stands for &quot;Navy Corps Investigative Service&quot;", "correct_answer": "False",
     "incorrect_answers": ["True"]}]
